<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>PineBoat</title>
    <link>https://pineboat.in/</link>
    <description>Recent content on PineBoat</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2017 20:18:38 +0530</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://pineboat.in/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Shipping beats perfection</title>
      <link>https://pineboat.in/post/shipping-beats-perfection/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2017 20:18:38 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pineboat.in/post/shipping-beats-perfection/</guid>
      <description>First of all, there is an elaborate post on this by Ben Kamens if you really want to know more on that phrase and what it means to software development.
For quite sometime I&amp;rsquo;ve been trying to create my own blog. I wanted to share what I learned. I was forgetting things faster than the rate at which I learned them (I am a web developer, enough said). I wanted to keep writing so that I can retain them longer and also help someone on the way (which could be the future-me trying to solve the same problem).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://pineboat.in/page/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Jun 2017 20:19:30 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pineboat.in/page/about/</guid>
      <description>Why When you tend to forget faster than you learn, one way to enhance retention is to write about it. That&amp;rsquo;s how it started. Also, others in need might reach here for help.
What Document all that is learned as practically as possible and make it available for everyone. A blog, naturally. Ruby on rails, CSS, javascript, TDD, React, Redux, Devops, Travis, Git, Nginx, Passenger, Puma, Postgresql, Virtualbox, Selenium, WebDriver, Software Testing&amp;mdash;so much learning, but when I hit the same problem again, I tend to search through the same set of forums and solve it a second time in the longest way possible.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://pineboat.in/author/vijayabharathib/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jun 2017 21:13:19 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pineboat.in/author/vijayabharathib/</guid>
      <description>Software quality assurance and test automation expert and a newbie full stack web developer.
Short-named as &amp;lsquo;VB&amp;rsquo; that aligns with my name and the many hours I spent on Visual Basic, when the name actually came about into existence.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>